Finding Aid for the Herbert Charles Sanborn Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Correspondence - Incoming, Incoming correspondence of 4,326 letters, 235 post cards, and 70 telegrams. Alphabetically arranged, letters are typescript, holograph, and carbon copies. There are several circular and mimeographed. 1 Letters signed with initials only and with 1 name only are found at e
  - Rives, Mrs. Al G. (33), Apr. 7, 1950, Apr. 15, 1950, Apr. 25, 1950, May 29, 1950, June 4, 1950, Aug. 15, 1950, Nov. 1, 1950, Feb. 23, 1951, Aug. 5, 1951, Aug. 18, 1951, Aug. 25, 1951, Sept. 26, 1951, Apr. 8, 1953,.- 31, 1954; Apr. 24, 1954 (post card), Oct. 19, 1954, Nov. 1, 1954, Nov. 9, 1954, Dec. 27, 1954 (post card), Jan. 16, 1955, Jan. 28,. 1955, Feb. 18, 1955, Oct. 13, 1955 (to United Air Lines, Inc.), July 1, 1956, Sept. 8, 1957, Oct. 1, 1957; Feb. 13, 1958, Mar. 21, 1958, Aug. 1, 1958, Aug. 18, 1958, Apr. 18, 1959, Mar. 20, (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Roach, Agnes D. (4), Dec. 12, 1949, Aug. 10, 1954, May 29, 1962, (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Roach, John (1), Dec. 20, 1944 (Box 12)
  - Robbins, Roy M. (1), Sept. 3, 1943 (to Jolm H. Melzer) (Box 12)
  - Roberts, David (2), Aug. 14, 1943, Apr. 24, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Roberts, Harry (1), Nov. 26, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Roberts, Stuart (3), Dec. 26, 1959, Dec. 26, 1959, Jan. 30, 1960 (Box 12)
  - Robertson, A. Willis (1), Apr. 13, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Robinson, Francis (11), July 20, 1943, Sept. 22, 1952, Sept. 26, 1952, Sept. 26, 1952 (to Hans Simons), Oct. 27, 1952. (to F. Adams), Oct. 28, 1952, Nov. 27, 1952, Dec. 1, 1952, Aug. 23, 1957, Dec. 14, 1959, Dec. 26, 1959 (Box 12)
  - Robinson, G.N. (1), May 10, 1953 (Box 12)
  - Robinson, J.R. (1), Feb. 14, 1929 (Box 12)
  - Robnett, George W. (2), Jan. 6, 1955, June 9, 1955 (Box 12)
  - Rochedieu, C.A. (2), July 31, 1951, Aug. 9, 1951 (Box 12)
  - Rock, Mary Edna (4), Dec. 21, 1942, Jan. 23, 1944, Jan. 24, 1944, Feb. 23, 1944 (Box 12)
  - Rocker, R. (1), May 11, 1944 (Box 12)
  - Rocker, Rudolph (1), Sept. 15, 1955 (to A.F. Kuhlman) (Box 12)
  - Rody, I. (1), Aug. 31, 1945 (Box 12)
  - Roehm, Dan C. (1), Oct. 29, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Rogers, Henry H. (1), Oct 11, 1955 (Box 12)
  - Rogers, Ruth (1), Dec. 28, 1962 (Box 12)
  - Rogers, Wm. F. (1), Mar. 29, 1923 (Box 12)
  - Rollins, Steed (7), July 26, 1942, Jan. 19, 1944 (to John Melzer), Jan. 25, 1945 (to John Melzer), Jan. 31, 1945, May 10, 1954, Mar. 6, 1956, Nov. 10, 1959 (Box 12)
  - Romer, Carl W. (1), Aug. 12, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Rooney, A. William (6), May 25, 1952, Dec. 19, 1952, Feb. 2, 1954, Mar. 8, 1954, June 28, 1954, (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Rooney, Robert C. (1), Sept.ll, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Rosenthal, Alice (1), Nov. 2, 1945 (Box 12)
  - Ross, Franz E. (1), Mar. 6, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Ross, Paul (1), July 26, 1956 (Box 12)
  - Roth, Wm. (3), July 5, 1933 (post card), Oct. 8, 1934, Apr. 12, 1935 (Box 12)
  - Rotsch, Cecil C. (3), Mar. 16, 1950, Mar. 29, 1950, Apr. 15, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Roy, Stanley G. (1), (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Rubel, Julius S. (2), Dec. 3, 1949, Dec. 28, 1949 (Box 12)
  - Rubino, Abbie (1), Aug. 7, 1933 (Box 12)
  - Rule, Mrs. Ehver D. (1), (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Runkle, Erwin W. (1), Mar. 15, 1927 (Box 12)
  - Runyon, Charles V. (1), ept. 30, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Russell, Dick (1), July 17, 1957 (Box 12)
  - Russell, Francia (1), Apr. 6, 1959 (post card) (Box 12)
  - Russell, Fred (2), Jan. 26, 1954, May 26, 1954 (Box 12)
  - Rust, Littell (1), May 20, 1952 (Box 12)
  - Ryan, James H. (1), Feb. 9, 1928 (Box 12)
  - Sadler, R. (1), Nov. 25, 1952 (Box 12)
  - Sager, Jesse (1), Mar. 25, 1947 (Box 12)
  - Salmon, Christopher V. (3), Feb. 19, 1950, Mar. 2, 1950, June 2, 1950 (Box 12)
  - Sammons, Wheeler (9), June 1, 1951, Dec. 8, 1952, Feb. 17, 1955, 1945, 1946, 1950, 1952, (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Sampson, Gus (1), Sept. 28, 1946 (Box 12)
  - Sanborn, Hra. Cummings Avery (1), Apr. 12, 1935 (Box 12)
  - Sanborn, Edith (19), July 20, 1930, Jan. 2, 1933, Jan. 7, 1933, Jan. 23, 1933, Jan. 24, 1933, Jan. 27, 1933, Aug. 4, 1933 (post card), Aug. 10, 1933, Aug. 21, 1933, Aug. 31, 1933, Sept. 5, 1933; Mar. 30, 1938 (post card), Nov. 2, 1952, Nov. 7, 1952, Aug. 3, Nov. 3, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 12)
  - Sanborn, Elenora (1), Aug. 1, 1934 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Frank E. (2), May 14, 1932, Nov. 19, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Frederic Rockwell (2), Mar. 26, 1933, Feb. 9, 1953 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Frederick Rodney (2), Feb. 11, 1944, Jan. 15, 1951 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Geo.P. (1), Sept. 16, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Jackie (7), Oct. 11, 1950, Nov. 16, 1950, Dec. 14, 1950, Oct. 1, 1952, Nov. 17, 1952, Feb. 12, 1957, Nov. 2, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Louise Kirkland (2), Apr. 18, 1932, May 14, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, M.Ray (1), Sept. 20, 1932 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Mary Moore (1), Aug. 31, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Phyliss (4), Nov. 25, 1945, Apr. 24, 1953, Mar. 14, 1958, Oct. 19, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, Uly (1), Feb. 2, 1919 (Box 13)
  - Sanborn, William H. (2), May 19, 1953, May 30, 1953 (post card) (Box 13)
  - Sandburg, Mrs. Carl (1), Apr. 2, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Sanders, Lillian (2), Nov. 4, 1946, Mar. 20, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Sanford, G.H. (1), (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Sarratt, C.M. (9), Oct. 25, 1945 (to Frank Pattie), Apr. 25, 1947, Dec. 17, 1949, Sept. 25, 1950, Mar. 8, 1951, Mar. 13, 1952, May 28, 1953, Feb. 2, 1954, Nov. 5, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Saville, L. Brooks (1), Oct. 5, 1925 (Box 13)
  - Sayer, John. (1), Sept. 4, 1934 (to G.F.Steele) (Box 13)
  - Schafer, Dietrich (1), Mar. 31, 1923 (Box 13)
  - Schanck, Richard L. (1), Mar. 18, 1942 (Box 13)
  - Schaub, E. (1), Mar. 19, 1927 (Box 13)
  - Scheurich, Rosalia A. (2), Jan. 30, 1944, Mar. 18, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Schieffelin, eorge McKay (1), Jan. 22, 1935 (Box 13)
  - Schiffman, Maurice K. (1), Nov. 25, 1942 (Box 13)
  - Schmutzler, Jack (5), Mar. 24, 1946, Mar. 25, 1 6, Apr. 1, 1946, Hay 6, 1946, May 7, 1946 (Box 13)
  - Schneider-Leyer, Dr. (1), Mar. 21, 1955 (Box 13)
  - Schott, Charles (1), Mar. 23, 1933 (Box 13)
  - Schultz, Henry Edward (1), Oct. 4, 1955 (to George E.Stratemeyer) (Box 13)
  - Schweitzer, Leonard J. (10), Mar. 14, 1945, Mar. 28, 1945, Apr. 14, 1945, June 15, 1945, July 2, 1945, July 23, 1945, Nov. 7, 1945, Jan. 2, 1946, Nov. 18, 1946, Nov. 25, 1946 (Box 13)
  - Scott, Ira W. Jr. (1), Oct. 4 (Box 13)
  - Scott, Leonard L. (1), Nov. 17, 1934 (Box 13)
  - Seabaugh, D.R. (2), May 29, 1946, Feb. 14, 1947 (Box 13)
  - Sears, Roebuck and Co. (2), Jan. 26, 1944, Mar. 29, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Seay, Joseph W. (1), Sept. 7, 1951 (Box 13)
  - Seed, Avis (1), July 10, 1956 (Box 13)
  - Seiller, Bill (1), Oct. 30, 1953 (Box 13)
  - Seip, Fred (2), Dec. 9, 1950, July 14, 1958 (Box 13)
  - Sellers, Ava F. (1), Jan. 12, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Sepp, T. (1), Nov. 27, 1949 (Box 13)
  - Shallenberger, M.C. (1), Nov. 2, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Shanks, Elsie (1), (n.d.); (to Editor, Popular Dogs) (Box 13)
  - Shannon, George Pope (2), Aug. 21, 1953, Aug. 20, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Sharpe, Harry (14), Oct. 29, 1945 (telegram), Nov. 2, 1945, Dec. 7, 1945, Dec. 17, 1945, Dec. 20, 1945, Apr. 24, 1946, June 28, 1948, Oct. 22, 1948, Aug. 18, 1949, June 6, 1950, Aug. 10, 1950, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Sharpe, Harry and Vivian (9), June 30, 1949, July 21, 1949, Nov. 14, 1949, Feb. 27, 1950, Feb. 24, 1951, Nov. 29, 1951, Oct. 16, 1952, July 9, 1954, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Shatto, Joe M. (1), Oct. 10, 1949 (Box 13)
  - Shea, M. Coyle (1), Sept. 15, 1935 (Box 13)
  - Shepard, Cornelia (2), Dec. 4, 1959, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Sheppard, H.Cecil (3), Jan. 28, 1944, Feb. 16, 1944, Dec. 4, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Sheshunoff, Wendell Austin (2), Oct. 19, 1949, May 20 (Box 13)
  - Sheward, John C. (5), Nov. 26, 1951, Jan. 1, 1952, Oct. 15, 1952, May 17, 1953, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Shively, Bernie A. (1), Aug. 23, 1957 (Box 13)
  - Shook, P.G. (1), May 31, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Shorey, Paul (2), Oct. 7, 1925, Sept. 21, 1927 (Box 13)
  - Short, C.H. (1), Nov. 24, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Shultis, Gene (1), Aug. 25, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Shultis, Mr. and Mrs. Hay E. (2), Nov. 9, 1949, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Shute, v1arence (1), (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Sias, Mildred (3), Feb. 19, 1950, Mar. 5, 1950, Mar. 15, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Sias, W.R. (3), Oct. 3, 1950, Oct. 20, 1950, Nov. 15, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Sidewater, Ab (2), Sept. 1, 1950, (post card), Nov. 28, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Sieja, Stanley S. (1), Feb. 1, 1951 (Box 13)
  - Siepl, E. (1), June 18, 1959 (to Martha Dingler) (Box 13)
  - Silva, Joao (1), ept. 18, 1936 (Box 13)
  - Silver, James. (3), Jan. 7, 1952, Feb. 11, 1952, Mar. 20, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Silver, Milton G. (1), (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Simmerman, J.P. (1), Nov. 14, 1945 (Box 13)
  - Simmons, Ernest J. (1), Sept. 25, 1953 (Box 13)
  - Sims, H.D. (12), Apr. 2, 1934, Sept. 27, 1934 (telegram), May 10, 1935 (telegram), May 14, 1935, May 29, 1935, July 3, 1935, Aug. 30, 1935, Oct. 16, 1935, Nov. 5, 1935 (telegram), Nov. 21, 1935, July 31, 1942, Jan. 17, 1944 (Box 13)
  - Sims, Mr.and Mrs. H.D. (2), Sept. 24, 1934, Oct. 10, 1934 (Box 13)
  - Sims, Jack (1), May 26, 1960 (post card) (Box 13)
  - Sinesal, Margaret L. (1), July 24, 1952 (Box 13)
  - Sisk, T.K. (1), May 28, 1924 (Box 13)
  - Sjolin, Ava-Lloyd (1), Oct. 10, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Skiles, Jonah W.D. (6), Nov. 23, 1951, May 12, 1952 (post card), May 20, 1952, Jan. 5, 1953, May 24, 1954, June 16, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Slonaker, Howard (3), Nov. 25, 1949 (telegram), Nov. 28, 1949, Dec. 16, 1949 (telegram) (Box 13)
  - Smart, Edwin J. (1), (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Smith, Alden H. (2), 1948, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Smith, C.J. (1), Oct. 12, 1943 (Box 13)
  - Smith, E.V. (1), Nov. 11, 1953 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Elizabeth B. (1), Feb. 24, 1953 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Florence (9), Sept. 27, 1949, Oct. 7, 1949, Nov. 16, 1949, Feb. 24, 1950, Mar. 20, 1950, Feb. 29, 1952, Feb. 1, 1955, Apr. 9, 1956, May 28, 1958 (post card) (Box 13)
  - Smith, George M. (1), June 17, 1943 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Gerald L.K. (39), Mar. 30, 1954, June 28, 1954, Aug. 22, 1957, June 23, 1958, Sept. 29, 1958, Jan. 29, 1959, Mar. 6, 1959, Mar. 30, 1959, pr. 17, 1959, Apr. 30, 1959, May 22, 1959, June 11, 1959; July 6, 1959, Aug. 19, 1959, Sept. 11, 1959, Oct. 15, 1959, Oct. 29, 1959, Nov. 9, 1959, Dec. 1, 1959, Dec. 9, 1959, Jan. 14, 1960, Jan. 25, 1960, June 14, 1960, May 11, 1962, May 28, 1962, July 2, 1962, July 12, 1962, July 18, 1962; Aug. 20, 1962, Aug. 29, 1962, Sept. 12, 1962, Nov. 15, 1962, Dec. 7, 1962, Dec. 17, 1962, Jan. 2, 1963, Jan. 10, 1963, Jan. 24, 1963, May 20, 1964, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Smith, J. Russell (1), Jan. 15, 1946 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Jane Buckley (1), Sept. 29, 1959 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Leonard S. Jr. (7), Oct. 21, 1943, Oct. 25, 1943, Nov. 30, 1943, Mar. 5, 1947, Mar. 31, 1947, Feb. 8, 1950, Feb. 23, 1950 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Mrs. Leonard S. Jr. (7), Oct. 25, 1945, Nov. 12, 1945, Apr. 26, 1950, June 19, 1951, July 11, 1951, Jan. 31, 1955, (n.d.) (Box 13)
  - Smith, Lillard (1), Feb. 12, 1946 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Lloyd C. (1), Feb. 28, 1946 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Maude Daniels (2), Apr. 23, 1944, June 10, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Robert W. (1), Aug. 23, 1954 (Box 13)
  - Smith, Thos. E. (8), Apr. 8, 1950 1 May 18, 1950, June 1, 1950, June 11, 1950, Oct. 16, 1950, Nov. 27, 1950, Dec. 8, 1950, July 5, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Soemisch, Marie (6), Mar. 1, 1934, May 2, 1934, Jan. 17, 1935, Feb. 19, 1935, May 8, 1935 (telegram), July 5, 1946 (Box 14)
  - Sokolsky, George E. (1), Jan. 29, 1949 (Box 14)
  - Somenzi, Vittorio (4), Aug. 29, 1952, Oct. 4, 1952, Aug. 31, 1954, Sept. 10, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Sonneman, Henry O. (1), May 18, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Sorantin, Eric (3), Nov. 28, 1935 (post card), Mar. 3, 1945, Mar. 20, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Southern Society for Philosophy and Psychology (1) (Box 14)
  - Southwestern Philosophical Conference (1), Oct. 1944 (Box 14)
  - Spanburgh, Christina (1), June 22, 1951 (post card) (Box 14)
  - Spangler, Fred T. (3), May 16, 1955, Jan. 29, 1957, Apr. 9, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Speidell, Charles F. Jr. (1), Apr. 15, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Sperry, J.J. (1), Feb. 23, 1953 (Box 14)
  - Spiller, Alma (1), June 7, 1951 (Box 14)
  - Spiro, Frank K. (1), Oct. 25, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Spivak, Lawrence E. (1), June 5, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Spradling, ueorge (1), Sept. 3, 1943 (Box 14)
  - Spratts Patent Ltd. (1), July 16, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Stackpole, E.J. (1), Nov. 17, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Stahlman, James G. (17), Dec. 15, 1949, Apr. 14, 1950, Sept. 13, 1950, Jan. 29, 1951, Feb. 6, 1951, Feb. 16, 1951, Nov. 7, 1951, Apr. 19, 1952, May 26, 1954, Aug. 16, 1954, Apr. 2, 1958, May 23, 1958; June 13, 1958, July 21, 1958, Sept. 25, 1959, July 18, 1960, Dec. 27, 1960 (Box 14)
  - Stapleton, Fielding P. (3), Jan. 18, 1935, May 4, 1935, July 2, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Stark Bros. Nurseries (1), May 9, 1935. (telegram) (Box 14)
  - Stark, Mildred (1), Oct. 13, 1943 (Box 14)
  - Stark, Stickney (2), May 9, 1935, May 17, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Stark, William C. (11), Apr. 20, 1944, May 8, 1944, July 14, 1944, Oct. 19, 1944, Dec. 7, 1944, Mar. 19, 1945 (to Roland), June 17, 1945, Nov. 5, 1945, Aug. 23, 1946, Apr. 16, 1952, July 16, 1953 (Box 14)
  - Stark, Mr. and Mrs. William C. (2), Nov. 30, 1951, (n.d.) (Box 14)
  - Starr, L.E. (1), Dec. 31, 1951 (Box 14)
  - Stearns, R.G. (1), Dec. 20, 1955 (to Lawrence P. Fahey) (Box 14)
  - Stearns, Richard G. (1), Jan. 10, 1957 (to Harris Burns, Jr.) (Box 14)
  - Steele, G.F. (3), Sept. 14, 1934, Jan. 21, 1935, Sept. 3, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Steele, Kate Hinds (1), Oct. 1, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Steele, R.B. (1), (n.d.) (Box 14)
  - Steele, Walters. (1), Oct. 7, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Steins, A. (1), Dec. 18, 1949 (Box 14)
  - Stekel, Wilhelm (1), (n.d.) (Box 14)
  - Stennis, John (1), Sept. 13, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Stephens, Bettie P. (2), July 27, 1943, Aug. 11, 1943 (Box 14)
  - Stephens, Mrs. Richard W. (2), Jan. 3, 1944, May 4, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stephens, T.C. (1), Dec. 8, 1924 (Box 14)
  - Stephenson, Mrs'.S.F. (1), Uec. 23, 1943 (Box 14)
  - Stetson, J.H. (1), Mar. 1, 1954 (Box 14)
  - Stevens, Lera (1), Oct. 24, 1957 (Box 14)
  - Stevensen, A.K. (1), Dec. 23, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stevenson, Ann (1), Feb. 7, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stevenson, Eugene H. (1), July 6, 1956 (Box 14)
  - Stewart, H. Francis (1), Aug. 31, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Stewart, Randall (5), Oct. 11, 1950, Oct. 2, 1952, Aug. 2, 1954 (post card), Aug. 6, 1958, Jan. 21, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Stickles, A.M. (1), May 1, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Stivers, .F'elix (2), Dec. 10, 1944, June 24 (Box 14)
  - Stoddard, C.N. (1), Oct. 12, 1948 (Box 14)
  - Stoddard, Elizabeth Sanborn (15), June 14, 1943, June 19, 1943 (post card), Uec. 13, 1943, July 5, 1944, Dec. 9, 1944, Dec. 5, 1945, Dec. 8, 1948, Nov. 9, 1949, Jan. 26, 1950 (post card); Apr. 15, 1950, Apr. 19, 1951, Aug. 9, 1951 (post card), Oct. 3, 1953, May 26, 1954, (n.d.) (Box 14)
  - Stokes, S.D. (1), Nov. 13, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stoltz, V.T. (3), Aug. 9, 1944, Aug. 17, 1944, Sept. 7, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stone, Calvin P. (1), Aug. 2, 1949 (post card) (Box 14)
  - Stovall, Elizabeth Sanborn (1), Apr. 14, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stow, Lloyd (1), Nov. 24, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Stratemeyer, George E. (1), Oct. 12, 1955 (to Henry E.Schultz) (Box 14)
  - Stratton, Sally (1), Mar. 30, 1955 (Box 14)
  - Street, Robert H. (1), Apr. 24, 1944 (Box 14)
  - Stroman, James H. (3), Apr. 21, 1958, Aug. 8, 1958, Apr. 18, 1959 (Box 14)
  - Stroud, Anna U. (1), Oct. 18, 1950 (Box 14)
  - Stroud, Charles C. (3), Feb. 5, 1933, Jan. 26, 1943, Feb. 20, 1945 (Box 14)
  - Stroud, Robert (1), Feb. 17, 1939 (Box 14)
  - Strunk, Caroline (2), Mar. 7, 1955, Jan. 16, 1956 (Box 14)
  - Strunk, D. Forest (1), Apr. 10, 1951 (Box 14)
  - Stuber, Elizabeth Davis (1), Sept. 24, 1935 (Box 14)
  - Stumpf, S.E. (1), Oct. 27, 1952 (Box 14)
  - Sullivan, Dorothy Sanborn (153), June 13, 1948, Sept. 10, 1949, Sept. 26, 1949, Oct. 18, 1949, Oct. 19, 1949, Nov. 11, 1949, Nov. 23, 1949, Dec. 19, 1949, Jan. 11, 1950 (telegram), Jan. 21, 1950, Jan. 28, 1950, Feb. 2, 1950, Feb. 3, 1950 (telegram); Feb. 7, 1950, Feb. 11, 1950, Feb. 15, 1950, Feb. 24, 1950, Feb. 27, 1950, Mar. 11, 1950, Mar. 27, 1950, Mar. 28, 1950 (telegram), Apr. 12, 1950, Apr. 21, 1950, May 2, 1950, May 10, 1950, May 18, 1950, May 25, 1950, June 4, 1950; June 11, 1950, June 27, 1950, July 5, 1950, July 24, 1950, July 26, 1950, Aug. 2, 1950, Bept. 3, 1950, Sept. 20, 1950, Oct. 6, 1950, Oct. 12, 1950, Oct. 26, 1950, Dec. 6, 1950, Uec. 12, 1950, Dec. 17, 1950, Dec. 26, 1950; Jan. 9, 1951, Jan. 15, 1951, Jan 21, 1951, Jan. 25, 1951, Feb. 5, 1951, Feb.?, 1951, Feb. 13, 1951, Mar.13, 1951, Apr. 6, 1951, Apr. 13, 1951, May 23, 1951, May 24, 1951, June 4, 1951, June 16, 1951, June 18, 1951; June 29, 1951, July 30, 1951, Aug. 7, 1951, Aug. 10, 1951, Aug. 31, 1951, Oct. 3, 1951, Oct. 10, 1951, Oct. 27, 1951, Nov. 26, 1951, Dec. 27, 1951, Feb. 5, 1952, Feb. 26, 1952, Apr. 4, 1952, May 7, 1952, June 12, 1952, June 27, 1952; July 24, 1952, Aug. 11, 1952, Sept. 8, 1952, Sept. 21, 1952, Oct. 13, 1952, Oct. 23, 1952, Oct. 25, 1952; Nov. 3, 1952, Nov. 18, 1952, Nov. 26, 1952, (telegram), Dec. 18, 1952 (telegram), Jan. 3, 1953, Feb. 11, 1953, Feb. 21, 1953, Mar. 10, 1953; Mar. 23, 1953, Apr. 7, 1953, pr. 21, 1953, Apr. 26, 1953, Apr. 30, 1953, May 12, 1953, June 5, 1953, June 24, 1953, July 21, 1953, Aug. 4, 1953, Aug. 10, 1953, Nov. 11, 1953, Feb. 27, 1954, Apr. 24, 1954, May 5, 1954, May 1;, 1954; May 20, 1954, May 29, 1954, June 14, 1954, July 17, 1954, Aug. 11, 1954, Aug. 13, 1954, Aug. 13, 1954 (telegram), ug. 29, 1954, Sept. 11, 1954, Sept. 18, 1954, Sept. 30, 1954; Oct. 12, 1954, Oct. 23, 1954, Nov. 6, 1954, Dec. 10, 1954, Jan. 1, 1955; Jan. 14, 1955, Feb. 5, 1955, Hay 4, 1955, May 14, 1955, Sept. 3, 1955, ept. 22, 1955, Jan. 2, 1956, Feb. 22, 1956; May 12, 1957, Mar. 19, 1958, Nov. 7, 1958, r. 25, 1959, June 1, 1959, Oct. 19, 1959, Dec. 24, 1959 (telegram), Aug. 10, 1961, (16 letters withoug dates) (Box 14, Box 15)
  - Sullivan, Gene (62), Jan. 13, 1950, Feb. 24, 1950, Mar. 24, 1950, July 12, 1950, Aug. 13, 1950, O t. 7, 1950, Nov. 5, 1950, Nov. 16, 1950, ec. 1, 1950, Dec. 20, 1950, Jan. 29, 1951, Feb. 14, 1951, Feb 22, 1951, Feb. 28, 1951 (post card); Mar. 5, 1951, Apr. 4, 1951, May 17, 1951, July 3, 1951, July 191 1951, Aug. 14, 1951, Nov. 6, 1951, Nov. 11, 1951; Jan. 5, 1952, Mar. 7, 1952, Mar. 19, 1952, May 15, 1952, May 17, 1952, Sept. 15, 1952, Oct. 6, 1952, Nov. 28, 1952, Dec. 7, 1952; Jan. 8, 1953, Feb. 28, 1953, Mar. 17, 1953, May 2, 1953, May 18, 1953, June 1, 1953, June 12, 1954, June 14, 1954, July 6, 1954, July 8, 1954, July 17, 1954, Oct. 4, 1954, Oct. 30, 1954, Jan. 27, 1955, Feb. 7, 1955; Mar. 1, 1955, Apr. 19, 1955, June 24, 1955, Nov. 29, 1955, Dec. 8, 1956, Mar. 23, 1957, Apr. 7, 1958, Oct. 22, 1958, Dec. 4, 1958; Jan. 27, 1959, Mar. 3, 1959, July 1, 1959, Apr. 10, 1960, (n.d.), (n.d.), (n.d.) (Box 15)
  - Sullivan, Gene and Dorothy (16), Jan. 12, 1949, Dec. 28, 1949, Feb. 23, 1950, Aug. 17, 1950, ept. 25, 1950, Nov. 4, 1950, Dec. 12, 1950, May 7, 1951, Feb. 13, 1952, Dec. 25, 1952, Mar. 2, 1953, Mar. 2, 1953, Jan. 25, 1955, Jan. 25, 1955 (post card) (Box 15)
  - Sulptine, Mrs. Dudley (1), Apr. 4, 1945 (Box 15)
  - Summers, Frank L. (1), Mar. 14, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Sutherlin, John H. (2), Feb. 18, 1952, Feb. 19, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Sutton, H.M. (1), Nov. 8, 1951 (Box 15)
  - Sutton, Pat (1), June 21, 1949 (Box 15)
  - Swan, Donald A. (4), Feb. 15, 1960, Jan. 16, 1961 (to Heinrich Quiring), Apr. 26, 1962, June 10, 1963 (to Robert Gayre) (Box 15)
  - Taber, Geo. L. Jr. (1), Mar. 8, 1945 (Box 15)
  - Taft, Hulbert (6), Nov. 14, 1944, Nov. 16, 1944, Nov. 17, 1944, Vee. 8, 1944, Dec. 10, 1945, Sept. 9, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Taft, Mrs. Hulbert (2), Dec. 30, 1944, Dec. 11 (Box 15)
  - Tainter, Alice Beatrice (1), Feb. 16, 1921 (Box 15)
  - Tate, Allen (7), Feb. 2, 1950, Oct. 12, 1950, Nov. 11, 1950, Jan. 12, 1951, Oct. 9, 1952, May 8, 1953, July 22, 1960 (Box 15)
  - Tate, Caroline (1), Nov. 30, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Tate, H. Clay (1), Sept. 24, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Tate, Mrs. Robert W. (3), June 13, 1946, June 17, 1946 (telegram), Aug. 24, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Tate, Toby Ray (2), Dec. 16, 1959, Dec. 29, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Tatham, Julie Campbell (1), Feb. 1, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Tatterson, Alice M. (1), Mar. 22, 1961 (Box 15)
  - Tavenner, Eugene (4), Nov. 5, 1951, Apr. 23, 1955, July 16, 1958, July 17, 1958 (post card) (Box 15)
  - Taylor, Alva W. (1), Apr. 27, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Taylor, Everett Ridley (8), Jan. 12, 1954, Dec. 15, 1954, Jan. 1, 1955, Jan. 31, 1955, Aug. 1, 1955, Sept. 1, 1955, Hay 12, 1956, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Taylor, James (1), Apr. 28,1955 (Box 15)
  - Taylor, Raymond L, (1), Feb. 20, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Taylor, Tyre (1), Aug. 12, 1960 (to A. Aruntunoff) (Box 15)
  - Teachers Insurance and Annuity Association (5), July 20, 1944, Sept. 29, 1944, Oct. 1, 1945, Oct. 1951, Oct. 1955 (Box 15)
  - Tebell, Gus K. (1), Nov. 1, 1955 (Box 15)
  - Teeter, D.D. (1), Apr. 17, 1944 (Box 15)
  - Ten Hoor, Marten (10), Apr. 22, 1935, Nov. 10, 1944, Jan. 8, 1945, Mar. 11, 1947, Mar. 10, 1950, Apr. 11, 1950, Jan. 31, 1951, Feb. 20, 1951, Sept. 1, 1951, Sept. 3, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Tennessee Federation for Constitutional Government (1), (n.d.) (Box 15)
  - Tennessee Nursery Company (1), Nov. 25, 1958 (post card) (Box 15)
  - Tennessee Society To Maintain Segregation (1), (n.d.) (Box 15)
  - Tennessee State Society Children of the American Revolution (1), (n.d.) (Box 15)
  - Tenney, Jack. (1), Sept. 28, 1954 (Box 15)
  - Terrell, Edna Hikes (2), July 2, 1946, Oct. 1, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Terrell, Edna and Lloyd (1), Oct. 30, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Teter, Mrs. F.W. (1), Aug. 30, 1944 (Box 15)
  - Thilly, Frank (2), Mar. 11, 1927, May 23, 1927 (Box 15)
  - Thomas, Alma (1), Aug. 1, 1950 (Box 15)
  - Thomas, Dilia and Kelly (1), Feb. 14, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Thomas, George. J. (5), Jan. 12, 1956, Mar. 1959, May 7, 1959, June 1959, June 1962 (Box 15)
  - Thomas, Leonard L. (1), May 3, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Thompson, B.V. Jr. (1), Dec. 8, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Thompson, H.Keith (7), Oct. 1, 1954, Nov. 18, 1954, Dec. 10, 1954, Jan. 8, 1955, May 5, 1958, June 10, 1958, May 25, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Thomson, Joanna D. (33), Aug. 3, 1942, Feb. 28, 1943, July 18, 1943, July 29, 1943, Aug. 3, 1943, Aug. 21, 1943, Sept. 1, 1943, Sept. 8, 1943, Sept. 19, 1943, Sept. 24, 1943, Sept. 25, 1943, Dec. 12, 1943, Mar. 30, 1944, Nov. 22, 1944, Nov. 26, 1944, May 14, 1945; July 17, 1945, Sept. 13, 1945, Sept. 18, 1945, Sept. 19, 1945, June 12, 1946, June 19, 1946, July 15, 1946, July 24, 1946; Oct. 10, 1946, Oct. 24, 1946, Feb. 11, 1947, May 18, 1948, June 23, 1953, Dec. 1, 1953, Dec. 9, 1953, Dec. 16, 1953, (n.d.) (Box 15)
  - Thurman, J. Clifton (1), Nov. 16, 1955 (post card) (Box 15)
  - Thurmond, Gilbert (1), Aug. 22, 1941 (Box 15)
  - Thurmond, Strom (1), July 19, 1954 (to James W.Perkins) (Box 15)
  - Tierney, Dorothy (1), uept. 3, 1952 (Box 15)
  - Tille, R. (2), Mar. 22, 1946, Apr. 11, 1946 (Box 15)
  - Time (Magazine) (1), June 26, 1951 (Box 15)
  - Tippens, James C. (1), Sept. 15, 1954 (Box 15)
  - Tobias, Charles H. (1), Dec. 22, 1958 (Box 15)
  - Toller, Mrs. F.N. (1), Oct. 1927 (Box 15)
  - Torue11a, Leticia (1), Sept. 4, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Trabue, Charles C. (1), Nov. 3, 1927 (Box 15)
  - Tripp, Beatrice Rapalje (1), Sept. 16, 1935 (Box 15)
  - Trotter, Frank B. (2), Nov. 11, 1930, Nov. 26, 1930 (Box 15)
  - Trumbauer, Walter H. (3), Nov. 12, 1950, Jan. 10, 1951, Apr. 22, 1951 (Box 15)
  - Tucker, Cornelia Dabney (1), July 15, 1955 (Box 15)
  - Tufts College (1), (n.d.) (Box 15)
  - Tuttle, Henry C. (2), Feb. 3, 1953, Apr. 11, 1959 (Box 15)
  - Turner, Jeannette (1), Sept. 28, 1954 (Box 15)
  - Turner, Mary Ellis (18), Sept. 29, 1940, Sept. 15, 1950 (post card), Nov. 27, 1950, Dec. 20, 1950, Dec. 20, 1990 (post card), Feb. 15, 1951, Mar. 22, 1951 (post card), Apr. 14, 1941 (post card), June 1, 1951 (post card), June 12, 1951 (post card); July 27, 1951 (poet card), Sept. 17, 1951, Jan. 25, 1952, Feb. 29, 1952, Mar.22, 1952, Sept. 22, Oct. 2, (n.d.) (Box 15)